<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Ako 的个人空间</title>
        <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Ako 的个人空间</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><managingEditor>akochen123666@gmail.com (Ako Chen)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>akochen123666@gmail.com (Ako Chen)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 15:12:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Modularity</title>
    <link>http://example.org/modularity/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 15:12:12 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Ako Chen</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/modularity/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Architecture</title>
    <link>http://example.org/architecture/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 22:55:34 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Ako Chen</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/architecture/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Layered Architecture 分层架构 Each layer represents a level of abstraction or specificity Provides higher-level services to the layer above it Relies on lower-level services from the layer below it Pure Form: Only Adjacent Layers Communicate. 只有相同的层之间可以通信。 Pros: Abstraction: One layer builds on another. Portability: Lower-level layers can be easily replaced. Cons: Performance: Communicating through layers.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Verification &amp; Validation and Testing</title>
    <link>http://example.org/testing/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 23:01:02 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Ako Chen</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/testing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Verification &amp; Validation Verification The process of evaluating a system/component to determine whether the products of a given development activity satisfy the conditions imposed at the start of that activity. 确定它是否符合早期定义的需求、标准和规范。 Validation The process of evaluating a system/component during or at the end of the development process to determine whether]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Requirement Engineering</title>
    <link>http://example.org/requirement/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:54:29 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Ako Chen</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/requirement/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A systematic approach to eliciting, organizing, and documenting the requirement of the system, and a process that establishes and maintains agreement between the customer and the project team on the changing requirements of the system. What does requirement mean? the things that the product must do to achieve its purpose functional requirements What the system does the qualities the product must have quality (aka non-functional) requirements How well the system]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>UML——Class Diagrams</title>
    <link>http://example.org/uml/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 16:04:59 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Ako Chen</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/uml/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Class Diagrams A dass diagram describes the types of objects in the System and the various kinds of static relationships that exist among them. 类图描述了系统中对象的类型以及它们之间存在的各种静态关系。 Attributes 特性 The attribute notation describes a property as a line of text within the class]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>软件工程的复习——设计模式</title>
    <link>http://example.org/first_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 16:36:49 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Ako Chen</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/first_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Design Patterns 设计模式 我第一次学习设计模式是在北京实习的时候突然给我派了一个攒一整个测试系统的工作，我开始研究哪一种设计模式是最合适的。虽然最后做出来]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
